[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How old was Drew Barrymore when she got engaged for the first time?", "correct_answer": "Sixteen", "incorrect_answers": ["Eighteen", "Seventeen", "Fourteen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the only Christopher Wren building in the Western Hemisphere?", "correct_answer": "in The College of William and Mary", "incorrect_answers": ["in Charleston, South Carolina", "in Philadelphia", "in Harvard University"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which science fiction movie contains these words, spoken by Elliot: He needs to go home, hes calling his people, and I dont know where they are, and he needs to go home.?", "correct_answer": "E.T. the Extra - Terrestrial", "incorrect_answers": ["The Ewok Adventure", "Fire in the Sky", "Flight of the Navigator"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 70s movie Carrie is based on a novel written by this famous author?", "correct_answer": "Stephen King", "incorrect_answers": ["Dean R. Koontz", "Ron Palillo", "Varese Sarabande"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What medical term refers to the fear of death or dying?", "correct_answer": "Thanatophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Dinophobia", "Triskadekaphobia", "Brontophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If we add up all the interior angles of a quadrilateral, what sum do we get?", "correct_answer": "360 degrees", "incorrect_answers": ["90 degrees", "540 degrees", "180 degrees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Gary Coopers character in the movie High Noon was originally named Will Doane. Co-star Katy Jurado had difficulty pronouncing Will Doane so the name was changed to this.", "correct_answer": "Will Kane", "incorrect_answers": ["Brett McBain", "Jonas Henderson", "Martin Howe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During this month of the pregnancy women go through a lot of mood swings like being easily irritated or start crying when they hear a song on the radio.", "correct_answer": "1st month", "incorrect_answers": ["7th month", "9th month", "4th month"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fletch from the self-titled movie visits Dr. Joseph Dolan to find out if Alan Stanwyk really has cancer. What song does Fletch start singing in the doctors office?", "correct_answer": "Moon River", "incorrect_answers": ["Pop Goes the Weasel", "Blue moon", "Singin in the Rain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In computer jargon, what is FTP?", "correct_answer": "a way to transfer files", "incorrect_answers": ["a programming language", "a popular Internet service provider", "a type of e-mail"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The motto of which US state is The Welfare of the People Shall Be The Supreme Law.?", "correct_answer": "Missouri", "incorrect_answers": ["Washington", "Connecticut", "Texas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of behavior is characteristic of scorpion species?", "correct_answer": "Photophobic behavior", "incorrect_answers": ["Hydrophobic behavior", "All of these", "Phonophobic behavior"]}]